[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Vietnam, a heroic nation, men and women
Việt Nam tôi dân tộc anh hùng gái trai
united in building a prosperous country. The heroic
một lòng dựng xây đất nước phồn
women of Vietnam, loving their
vinh người con gái nước nam oai hùng yêu
kind, marrying elephants, breaking bamboo poles,
giống ni cưới voi sng trơn gãy tầm vồng
defeating all kinds of monsters. The
đánh tan các loài sâm
Vietnamese men, invincible, the Southern Kingdom's mountains and rivers, the
l trai Việt Nam sư vang bất bại Nam Quốc
Southern Emperor's destiny, the
Sơn Hà Nam Đế
heavenly book, how
Cệt niên định phận tài thiên
dare the invaders come, the monsters come, the
thư như hà nghịch lỗ lai sâm
common people are like a vine, watching the enemy's defeat.
phàm như đằng hành khán thù bại
My Vietnam, a loyal nation, leading
hương Việt Nam tôi dân tộc trung kiên
to the home, women fighting and shouting, Ho Chi
dắt đến nhà đàn bà cung đánh hô Hồ Chí
Minh.
Minh
Waiting for the days of the
Đợi dằn đinh
Hung Kings who had the merit of building the nation.   We must work
ni các vua Hùng đã có công dựng nước.
together to protect our country.
Bác cháu ta phải cùng nhau giữ lấy nước.
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
I love Vietnam,
Tôi yêu Việt Nam
my blood is
tôi dòng máu đạc
more precious than fame, forever remembered for its glorious
hơn danh mãi lưu
victories.
vàng chiến thắng ngoài
I love Vietnam,
vang tôi yêu Việt Nam
my blood is more precious than wisdom and peace.
tôi dòng máu lạc hơn bí trí hiên hòa.
Integration leads to national
Hội nhập đề đất nước thăng
prosperity.  My Vietnamese people are heroic, men and
hoa. Việt Nam tôi dân tộc anh hùng gái
women united in heart and mind.
trai một lòng.
Stop building a
Dừng xây đất
prosperous and beautiful country
nước phồn vinh đẹp
.  I love my Vietnam.  I love
xinh. Tôi yêu Việt Nam tôi. Tôi yêu Việt
Vietnam.  I love my Vietnam.  I love
Nam. Tôi yêu Việt Nam tôi. Tôi yêu Việt
Vietnam.  I love
Nam. Tôi yêu Việt
Vietnam.  The
Nam. Dòng
bloodline is mixed.
máu lạc hơ.
[music]
[âm nhạc]
M.
M.